<resources>
    <string name="app_name">EtherPay</string>
    <string name="title_activity_send">SendActivity</string>
    <string name="no_acct">You have not set up an Ether account yet.
        Before using this app you need to import an Ether account using
        the "import account" menu item.
    </string>
    <string name="scan_addr_prompt">
    Scan the QR code that represents the reqipient address. Once the recipient
    address has been identified, you will be able to specify the amount of Ether
    that you would like to send.
    </string>
    <string name="scan_key_prompt">
    Scan the QR code that represents the private key for the account that you want
    to import.
    \n\nHint: To get a QR code for the private key for your account, you can visit
    https://www.myetherwallet.com and select the view-wallet-info tab.
    </string>
    <string name="ask_delete_old_key">This version of Etherpay only supports
    a single account. If you import a new account, then you erase your
    current account &#8212; (the account still exists, of course, but you will need
    to re-import it if you want to use it with Etherpay).
    </string>
    <string name="welcome">
      EtherPay is an Ether wallet app. &#8212; use it to check the balance in an Ether
      account; or to send or receive Ether to/from other Ether addresses.
      \n\nTo use the app, the first thing you need to do is import an Ether account.
      You need to use some other Ether client to create an account &#8212; I recommend
      https://www.myetherwallet.com/. Even of you already have a wallet, in order
      to import it you\&apos;ll need to get the private key, which you can do at
      myetherwallet.com, (under the view wallet info tab). Once you have the private key,
      to import it into the EtherPay app select the \"import account\" menu item.
      \n\nNOTE: The EtherPay app is *not* an \"Ethereum node\"&#8212;it uses etherchain.org
      to check your Ether balance; it uses your private key to sign transactions; and it uses
      etherscan.io to broadcast signed transactions. Your private key is never transmitted.
    </string>
    <string name="about">
    EtherPay is an Ether wallet app.
      \n\nI wrote it, honestly, because I love the whole concept of Ethereum, and I wanted
      to contribute in some way; and because I couldn\&apos;t find a simple Ether wallet for my
      smartphone.
      \n\nEther is usually not marketed as a currency &#8212; it is the way to pay for
      computation on the Ethereum distributed computing platform. But in my eyes this gives Ether
      an intrinsic value, in a way that is absent from other crypto-currencies. And the fact that
      Ether has intrinsic value, combined with it\&apos;s fast transaction time, 15 seconds, makes
      Ether perfect as a currency. Ulimately I believe that Ether will be widely used as a currency;
      and it\&apos;s intrinsic usability will simply ensure that it\&apos;s value cannot be zero
      (much as gold has intrinsic value, because of it\&apos;s beauty and maleablity; and therefore
      it is a natural currency).
      \n\nOne of the reasons that I would like to see the wide adoption of crypto-currencies, in
      general, and Ether in particular, is that I am a big fan of the Fourth Amendment of the U.S.
      Constitution, which provides:
      \n\n\"the right of the people to be secure in their persons, houses, papers, and
      effects, against unreasonable searches and seizures.\"
      \n\nThat is, I believe people ought to have privacy &#8212; and the anonymity of
      crypto-currencies is an important a step in that direction.
      \n\nThe EtherPay app is free; Please use it in good health! I plan to make other products
      to help people adopt Ether as a general-use currency.
      \n\nDavid Rosen, author of EtherPay.
    </string>
    <string name="receive_qr_prompt">
    This QR code represents your public account address. You need to provide this address to
    any  person, in order for them to send you Ether. You can allow people to scan the address
    directly from your phone, or you can share it, using the share button below.
    \n\nNote: It generally takes about 15 seconds for an Ether transaction to affect your
    balance.
    </string>
    <string name="min_sec_between_pays">
    You cannot send multiple payments in a rapid-fire sequence &#8212; To ensure that your
    payments are processed in order, please wait at least 30 seconds between consequitive
    payments.
    </string>
</resources>
